gigsalad.com 2018-11-03

# Privacy Policy - GigSalad

### Introduction

The Gig Bureau, LLC d/b/a GigSalad, a Delaware limited liability company (“ _GigSalad_ ,” “ _we_ ,” “ _us_ ,” or “ _our_ ”) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * by way of the www.gigsalad.com website (the “ _Site_ ”);
  * by way of the downloadable GigSalad mobile software application (the “ _App_ ”);
  * by way of all other products or services offered by GigSalad;
  * in email, text, and other electronic messages between you and GigSalad; and
  * when you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.

The Site, the App, and all other products or services offered by GigSalad are hereafter referred to collectively as the “ _Services_.”

This policy does _not_ apply to information collected by:

  * us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or
  * any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Services. By accessing or using our Services, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

### **Children Under the Age of 13**

Our Services are not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or on the Services. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us right away.

### **Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It**

_Types of Information Collected._ We collect several types of information from and about users of our Services, including information:

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, or ANY OTHER INFORMATION THE SERVICES COLLECT THAT IS DEFINED AS PERSONAL OR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION UNDER AN APPLICABLE LAW (collectively, “ _Personal Information_ ”);
  * that is about you but individually does not identify you; and/or
  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Services and usage details.

_Sources of Information Collection._ We collect such information:

  * directly from you when you provide it to us;
  * automatically as you navigate through the Services (including usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies); and
  * from third parties, for example, our business partners and service providers.

_Information You Provide to Us._ The information we collect on or through our Services may include the following information provided to us by you:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Services. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Services, subscribing to our Services, posting material, or requesting further Services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem or complaint relative to our Services.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Services and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Services.
  * Your search queries within the Services.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “ _posted_ ”) on public areas of the Services, or transmitted to other users of the Services or third parties (collectively, “ _User Contributions_ ”). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Services with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

_Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies._ As you navigate through and interact with our Services, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

  * details of your visits to our Site and other Services, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Services; and
  * information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and may include Personal Information, or we may maintain it or associate it with Personal Information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Services and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * estimate our user base size and usage patterns;
  * store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Services according to your individual interests;
  * speed up your searches; and
  * recognize you when you return to our Services.

The technologies we use for such automatic data collection may include:

  * **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Services. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Services.
  * **Web Beacons.** Portions of our Services and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

### **How We Use Your Information**

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any Personal Information:

  * to provide our Services and their contents to you;
  * to provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us;
  * to fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it;
  * to provide you with notices about your account/subscription, including expiration and renewal notices;
  * to carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection;
  * to notify you about changes to our Services;
  * to allow you to participate in interactive features on our Services;
  * in any other way we may describe when you provide the information; or
  * for any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third-parties’ goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please adjust your user preferences in your account profile. For more information, see “ _Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information_ ” below.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your Personal Information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

### **Disclosure of Your Information**

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose Personal Information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * to our subsidiaries and affiliates;
  * to contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business;
  * to any buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of GigSalad’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which Personal Information held by GigSalad about our Services users is among the assets transferred;
  * to third parties to market their products or services to you if you have not opted out of these disclosures (for more information, see “ _Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information_ ” below);
  * to fulfill the purpose for which you provide it;
  * for any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information; or
  * with your consent.

We may also disclose your Personal Information:

  * to comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request;
  * to enforce or apply our Terms of Use for GigSalad Services, Terms of Use for Trademark Dispute System, and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes;
  * in the process of processing, reviewing, or acting upon any notification or complaint we receive alleging infringement or violation of someone’s trademark rights, copyright interests, or other intellectual property rights; or
  * if we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of GigSalad, our customers, or others.

### **Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information**

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the Personal Information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
  * **Promotional Offers from the Company.** If you do not wish to have your email address/contact information used by the Company to promote our own or third parties’ products or services, you can opt-out by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data or at any other time by logging into the Services and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an email stating your request to **_help@gigsalad.com_**. If we have sent you a promotional email, you may click the unsubscribe link to opt out of all future email distributions. This opt out does not apply to information provided to GigSalad as a result of a purchase of Services, product service experience or other transactions with GigSalad.

### **Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of certain of our Services that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to **_help@gigsalad.com_** or write us at: 2733 E. Battlefield Rd., Box 105, Springfield, MO 65804.

### **Data Security**

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Services, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Services. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Services.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Services. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not, and cannot be, responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Services.

### **Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. Any changes of this privacy policy will apply prospectively, from the date the modifications are made, as designated by the “Last Revised” date depicted above. You will be given notice of any material changes by: (a) the updating of the “Last Revised” date, above, and (b) an email sent to you by us at the address you designate by clicking here, in the event you choose to designate an email address. If you choose not to designate an email address, you expressly agree that, by updating the “Last Revised” date when modifications are made, we are providing you with sufficient notice of such changes, and that your continued use of the Services subsequent to any modifications will constitute acceptance of this privacy policy as so changed.

### **Contact Information**

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us.
